obsev.com 2017-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Obsev

Effective Date: May 28, 2014

This Shandy Media, Inc. Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how we collect and use your information through our websites and services. We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time effective upon its posting. If we make revisions to this Privacy Policy, the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are aware of our most current policies and practices. Your continued use of our websites or services constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any updates. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms of Service.

 **1\. Types of Information Collected**

We collect information you give us and information we receive from your use of our websites or services. The information we collect may include, but is not limited to, your full name, gender, email address, mailing address, telephone number, social media information and profile, device identifiers and hardware information, IP address, browser and system type, access times, cookie information, location information (including but not limited to GPS information), activity and performance information, information about your purchases, and when necessary, credit card information.

You give us information in order to participate in activities including, but not limited to, sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, chats, bulletin boards, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. We automatically collect information regarding your interaction with, and use of our websites or services, and information available from your web browser. We may also obtain information from third-parties.

We may use cookies to store information regarding your use of our websites and services. This information may include, but is not limited to, your password, your preferences for a personalized home page, information about your activities on our websites and services, and other personal information. Note that our websites may not recognize or respond to Do Not Track (DNT) headers from web browsers.

 **2\. Use of Your Personal Information**

We will use your personal information for the purposes for which it was provided, and may use personal information for other purposes. For example, if you provide personal information to register for a newsletter, or to enter a contest or a sweepstake, or to purchase goods or services, we will use it to register you for or provide you with those goods or services. We may also use your personal information to provide you with information about features, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you. We also may send information or offers to selected groups of the users of our websites or services on behalf of us or other businesses, and your continued use of our websites and services constitutes your agreement to receive such information or offers. Under certain circumstances (for example if you win a contest) we may post your personal information to our websites or services. We will notify you of this possibility when you provide the personal information and, if possible, when the personal information is posted.

We may also share your personal information with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with us, but would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, some of the companies who supply prizes for our contests may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to users of our websites or services. We will never share your credit card information with third-parties except those we use to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through our websites or services.

We may also enter into agreements with outside companies to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our websites or services. Your personal information may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the “Google Analytics” cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the “DoubleClick” cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our websites or services. Additionally, we use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

There may be instances when we may disclose personal information in order to protect our legal rights, to protect the safety and security of visitors to our websites or services, to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes, or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if we sell all or part of our business or make a sale or transfer of assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may transfer your personal information to a third-party as part of that transaction.

 **3\. Third-Party Advertising and Links to Other Websites or Services**

Our websites and services include third-party advertising. These third-parties, or other third-parties that work on their behalf, may send (or “serve”) the advertisements that appear on our websites or services. These third-parties automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These third-parties may also use cookies, Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies to determine how long visits last and other associated information, deliver advertisements, and to collect personal information. We do not control how these advertisers collect personal information. Visitors to our websites or services should check the Privacy Policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it collects personal information. These companies may not recognize or respond to DNT headers from web browsers. Some third-parties allow you to opt-out of, or customize your preferences regarding, third-party advertisements and services.

Specifically, our websites and services make use of Google’s “Google Analytics” platform in order to collect data about where traffic to our websites and services originates, how long visits last, and other associated information. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit Google’s official Google Analytics webpage [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/). We have implemented a number of Google Analytics “Display Advertising” features on our websites and services, including “Remarketing,” “Google Display Network Impression Reporting,” the “DoubleClick Campaign Manager” integration, and “Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.” You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Dispay Advertising and customize Google Display Networks ads [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Google also offers other opt-outs for Google Analytics [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Alternatively, you can opt-out of the collection of data by Google and certain other advertising service providers at the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Please note that our websites and services contain links to other websites or services that will not follow this Privacy Policy. For instance, clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on our websites or services may take you to an entirely different website or service. Links to other websites or services may use our logos or styles as a result of a co-branding agreement. These websites or services may independently send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data not in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other websites or services. You should check the applicable privacy policy to determine how other websites or services will handle personal information or any other data collected from or provided by you.

 **4\. Protection and Security of Personal Information**

We use reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard personal information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third-parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

 **5\. Children and Privacy**

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the websites or services visited by their children. At various places on our websites and services, we may ask users for their age. By using our websites or services you agree to respond truthfully and accurately about your age. Children under the age of 13 years of age are expressly prohibited from submitting or posting any personal information to our websites or services.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

 **6\. Personal Information Posted to Message Boards, Chat Rooms, Blogs and Other User Forums**

Please remember that information posted to message boards, chat rooms, blogs and other user forums becomes public information. Use caution when posting. Individuals under the age of 18 should be especially careful not to provide any personal information when participating in any area of our websites or services.

 **7\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please write to Privacy, c/o Shandy Media, Inc. at 263 W Olive Ave #137, Burbank, CA 91502.
